famousdaves.com 2007-12-12

# Privacy Policy

**_Famous Dave's Internet Privacy Policy_**

Famous Dave’s respects the privacy of our guests.  This policy provides information about how we collect and use information on-line.

_Types of Information We Collect_

When voluntarily submitted through a form, e-mail, or online ordering, Famous Dave’s will collect your personal information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, birth date, and billing information.  This information will be used to process your orders for gift cards, send e-mail birthday wishes and news (through our P.I.G. Club), respond to feedback, or respond to franchising or hiring or other general inquiries.  With the exception of affiliates and Famous Dave’s franchisees, Famous Dave’s does not sell or share your information to third parties without your permission.

_Cookies_

Famous Dave’s may also use cookies to record session information, such as items added to the shopping cart.

In addition to voluntarily submitted information, we also use tracking information that is not personally identifiable in order to improve our website.  This is information such as most-visited web pages, referring page, browser type, or length of visit.

_Linked Websites_

Famous Dave’s website may include links to other websites.  These may include websites such as [www.famousbbq.com](http://www.famousbbq.com/) to order sauces and more, or [www.amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/) to order the _Famous Dave’s Backroads & Sidestreets Cookbook_.  These sites are not owned nor are they operated by Famous Dave’s and you should check those sites for their Privacy Policy which may differ from Famous Dave’s.

_Changes to Our Policy_

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2007.  Famous Dave’s reserves the right to change this policy at any time.  Any changes to this policy will be posted to this web page and will be effective from that date forward.

_Guest Relations_

If you have questions or concerns about our Internet Privacy Policy, please contact [Guest Relations](mailto:guestrelations@famousdaves.com).
